georgiapellegrini.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy - GeorgiaPellegrini.com

**Please read this Privacy Policy and our  [Terms of Service](http://georgiapellegrini.com/terms-of-service/) carefully before using this Web site.**

This Privacy Policy applies to the Web site  **[http://www.georgiapellegrini.com](http://www.fourhourworkweek.com/ "Link will open in a new window")**  and all associated sites (the “Site”).  This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect on the Site and how Georgia Pellegrini Media Group, Inc. and associated companies (“we,” “our” or “us”) uses it, the choices you can make about your information and how we protect your information.

**Information that we collect and how we use it**

We collect your name and email address. For example, you may subscribe to receive email updates from the blog on the Site by submitting your email address. You also may submit comments to the blog on the Site or through the contact mechanism on the Site. We generally do not encourage the submission of any personal information in these comments or through the contact mechanism other than what we expressly require (e.g., name and email address). Information you disclose in the comments becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your information in a submission.

Web servers may automatically capture the following information from visitors to the Site, including the name of the domain and host from which you access the internet, the internet address of the Site from which you enter the Site, the pages you visit on the Site and the amount of time you spend on the Site.  This visitor information may be used to improve the Site.

**Disclosure of information**

We will not voluntarily share your name and email provided via the Site to any third party, except:

– With third parties that we hire to perform services for us (these third parties are not authorized to keep or use your personal information for any other purpose),

– To comply with legal requirements, such as law, regulation, warrant, subpoena, court order, or with a regulator or law enforcement agency or personnel or

– In connection with a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, acquisition, dissolution or similar event.

Visitor information described above under “Information that we collect and how we use it” may be provided to third parties as described below under “Cookies“ and “Web Beacons.”

**Your choices and access**

We want to keep your name and email address accurate.  You can correct or update your name or email address that you have provided us.  Corrections can be submitted by emailing info [at] georgiapellegrini (dot) com. Readers dissatisfied with a response may reach us via email at robert [at] kleinmanlawfirm (dot) com.

The Site may allow you to choose to receive or stop receiving communications from us. You can prevent further use of your name or email address by submission by emailing info [at] georgiapellegrini (dot) com. Readers dissatisfied with a response may reach us via email at robert [at] kleinmanlawfirm (dot) com.

**Links to other Web sites**

We do not endorse and are not responsible for the information practices or privacy policies of any other Web sites that may be linked to or from the Site.  If you decide to access any other Web site that may be linked to or from the Site, you should consult that Web site’s privacy policy.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that the Site can place on your computer’s hard drive. When you visit the Site, a cookie may be placed on your computer for customizing and enhancing your experience on the Site. Your name and email address are not shared in this cookie. We use a cookie that collects anonymous traffic data. You can set your Web browser to block cookies, but doing so may affect your ability to access certain features of the Site.

**Web Beacons**

Web beacons are small bits of code embedded in Web pages or in emails. Web beacons may be used to deliver or communicate with cookies, to count users who have visited a Web page and to understand usage patterns. Web beacons also may be included in emails to learn if messages have been opened, acted on or forwarded. You can disable the ability of Web beacons to capture information in this manner by blocking cookies as described above under “Cookies.”

**Security**

We take reasonable steps to protect personal information from loss and misuse. Please keep in mind that no Internet transmission is 100% secure. Some email sent to or from the Site may not be secure. Please consider this when sending information to us by email.

**Children’s Privacy**

The Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect personal information from them. If we discover that a child has provided us with personal information, we will use reasonable efforts to delete this information. If you have reason to believe we may have accidentally received personal information from a child under the age of 13, please immediately submit details by emailing info [at] georgiapellegrini (dot) com. Readers dissatisfied with a response may reach us via email at robert [at] kleinmanlawfirm (dot) com

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We may modify, alter or update this Privacy Policy at any time. We will not provide individual notice to you of changes to this Privacy Policy, but when we make updates to this Privacy Policy, we will update the date in this section.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 3, 2018 **.**
